National Injury Bureau Privacy Policy
=====================================

**LAST UPDATED:** June 30, 2020

Thank you for visiting the National Injury Bureau website located at rounduprisk.com (the “Site”). The Site is an Internet property of National Injury Bureau (“Company,” “we,” “our” or “us”). This National Injury Bureau Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy“) covers our treatment of personal information and other information that we collect when an end-user visitor to the Site (“User," “you" or “your"): (a) accesses or uses the Site; (b) accesses and/or views any of the: (i) links (“Third-Party Links”) to resources and/or information pertaining to prospective legal services associated with medical malpractice, product liability, personal injury and/or other legal matters, as well as related products and/or services (collectively, “Legal Matters”); and/or (ii) text, video and/or other information pertaining to the Legal Matters, as well as related products and/or services, as made available on the Site (the “Informational Content”, and together with the Third-Party Links, the “Content”); (c) accesses links to Company’s social media pages/accounts featured on third-party social media websites, such as Facebook®, LinkedIn® and Twitter® (collectively, “Social Media Pages”); and/or (d) utilizes the various contact forms and/or contact information made available on the Site as a means to contact directly, or request to be contacted by, Company and/or attorneys (collectively, the “Third-Party Legal Professionals”) associated with the Legal Matters specified by you on the contact form (collectively, the “Contact Services,” and together with the Site, Content and Social Media Pages, the “Site Offerings”).

Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meanings set forth in the National Injury Bureau Terms and Conditions (“Terms and Conditions“).

Users with disabilities who wish to access this Privacy Policy in an alternative format can contact us by emailing us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com); calling us at: (833) 757-0886; or sending us U.S. Mail to: 300 Carlsbad Village Dr. 108A-516, Carlsbad, CA 92008.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO/WITH TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY IN THEIR ENTIRETY, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE OFFERINGS.

When you register on our Site, you hereby agree and acknowledge that your personal information will be placed into the Company database and that such personal information shall be shared with third parties for marketing purposes.

Facebook® is a registered trademark of Facebook, Inc. ("Facebook"). LinkedIn® is a registered trademark of LinkedIn Corporation (“LinkedIn”). Twitter® is a registered trademark of Twitter, Inc. ("Twitter"). Please be advised that Company is not in any way affiliated with Facebook, LinkedIn or Twitter, and the Site Offerings are not endorsed, administered or sponsored by any of the aforementioned entities.

Privacy Policy Quick Links
--------------------------

Below are links to key sections of our Privacy Policy:

Your California Privacy Rights
------------------------------

_Shine the Light._ If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to learn how your “personal information” (as defined in the Shine the Light Law, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83) is shared with third-parties, what categories of personal information we have shared with third-parties in the preceding year, as well as the names and addresses of those third-parties, please e-mail us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com); call us at: (833) 757-0886; or send us U.S. Mail to: 300 Carlsbad Village Dr. 108A-516, Carlsbad, CA 92008.

Further, if you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third-party for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com); call us at: (833) 757-0886; or send us U.S. Mail to: 300 Carlsbad Village Dr. 108A-516, Carlsbad, CA 92008. Please be advised that where California State residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with applicable law.

_California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”)._ In addition to the foregoing, if you are a resident of the State of California, certain other privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the CCPA, including the right to opt-out of our sale of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. Please see our “[Privacy Provisions for California Residents](https://rounduprisk.com/ccpa/)” below for a more complete description of your rights under the CCPA as a California State resident.

_Browser “Do Not Track” Signals._ Most browsers contain a “do-not-track” setting. In general, when a “do-not-track” setting is active, the user’s browser notifies other websites that the user does not want her/his personal information and online behavior to be tracked and used, for example, for interest-based advertising. As required by California Online Privacy Protection Act (“CalOPPA”), we are required to inform you that, as is the case with most websites, we do not honor or alter our behavior when a Site User has activated the “do-not-track” setting on her/his browser.

Your Nevada Privacy Rights
--------------------------

Nevada State residents have the right to submit opt-out requests to website operators instructing those website operators not to sell any “covered information” that the website operators have collected about the Nevada State residents to any third party data broker(s). Covered information includes a consumer’s name, postal and email address, telephone number and Social Security Number, and includes the Information described below in the “Personal Information that We Collect” section.

If you are a Nevada State resident and you wish to exercise your right to request that we to stop the sale of your Information to third party data brokers, please e-mail us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com); call us at: (833) 757-0886; or send us U.S. Mail to: 300 Carlsbad Village Dr. 108A-516, Carlsbad, CA 92008. In your request, please specify that you want to exercise your rights to opt-out from the sale of covered information under the Nevada Privacy Law and specify the website that you visited and the email address you registered with. Please allow thirty (30) days for a response.

Personal Information that We Collect
------------------------------------

Please see our [Privacy Provisions for California Residents](https://rounduprisk.com/ccpa/) below for additional details regarding the categories of personal information collected.

We collect your personally identifiable information when you access the Site Offerings, including the Contact Services, by and through the Site. We may also collect your personally identifiable information when you otherwise agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, but do not complete the applicable registration process in full. The types of personally identifiable information that we collect on the Site include, without limitation: (a) the User’s full name; (b) the User’s e-mail address; (c) the User’s telephone number; (d) the User’s zip code; (e) the User’s date of birth; (f) whether the User has already obtained legal representation; (g) questions pertaining to the type of Legal Matter that the User is inquiring about (e.g. type of medical condition suffered, product usage duration, etc.); and (h) any other information requested on the applicable form.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, any information pertaining to a User’s medical condition shall be treated as Sensitive Information.

How We Use Personal Information
-------------------------------

Use and Sharing of Personal Information
---------------------------------------

Please see our [Privacy Provisions for California Residents](https://rounduprisk.com/ccpa/) below for details regarding our use and sharing of personal information.

By submitting your personal information by and through the Site Offerings, you agree that we may share, sell, rent, lease or otherwise provide that personal information (other than Sensitive Information) to any third party for any purpose permitted by law, and we may work with other businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our Users. These businesses and third parties may include, but are not limited to: (a) providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation; (b) e-mail marketers; (c) telemarketers (where permitted by applicable law); and (d) direct marketers. We will also use your personal information to send you promotional messages regarding various Company products and/or services, as well as third party products and/or services that we think may be of interest to you.

Without limiting the foregoing, upon entering personal information and clicking on the applicable submission button on the Site, Company may pass your personal information (including Sensitive Information) along to one (1) or more of Company’s Third-Party Legal Professionals.

We may also employ third parties and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf, including helping us operate the Site Offerings and/or to administer related activities on our behalf. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from User lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these limited functions on our behalf shall have access to our Users’ personal information as needed to perform their functions for us, but we do not permit them to use User personal information for other purposes.

Additionally, we purchase and manage e-mail lists generated by third parties. Users may remove themselves from a specific mailing list by utilizing the unsubscribe options that are present and available at the end of each piece of e-mail that we send.

We will also use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request, to customize your experience on the Site and/or to contact you when necessary in connection with transactions entered into by you through the Site Offerings. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our business. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources.

By registering at the Site, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR §310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the “Rule”) and applicable state do-not-call regulations. As such, notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, and/or on applicable state do-not-call lists, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Rule and applicable state do-not-call regulations.

Where you provide “prior express consent” within the meaning of the Telephone Consumer Protection Act (47 USC § 227), and its implementing regulations adopted by the Federal Communications Commission (47 CFR § 64.1200), as amended from time-to-time (“TCPA“), you consent to receive telephone calls from Company and any specified Third-Party Provider(s), including artificial voice calls, pre-recorded messages and/or calls (including SMS text messages) delivered via automated technology, to the telephone number(s) that you provided. Please note that you are not required to provide this consent in order to obtain access to the Site Offerings, and your consent simply allows Company and any specified Third-Party Legal Professional(s) to contact you via these means. **Please be advised that by agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you are obligated to immediately inform us if and when the telephone number that you have previously provided to us changes. Without limiting the foregoing, if you: (a) have your telephone number reassigned to another person or entity; (b) give up your telephone number so that it is no longer used by you; (c) port your telephone number to a landline or vice versa; or (d) otherwise stop using that telephone number for any reason (collectively “Phone Number Change”), you agree that you shall promptly notify Company of the Phone Number Change via e-mail at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com), or by using one of the methods set forth in the “Contact Us” section below.**

We also reserve the right to release current or past User information (including Sensitive Information) in the event that we believe that the User is using, or has used, our products, services and/or Site: (i) in violation of the Terms and Conditions, this Privacy Policy or any other of our operating rules, policies, price schedules and other supplemental terms and conditions or documents that may be published by us from time to time; (ii) to commit unlawful acts; (iii) if such information is subpoenaed; provided, however, that, where permitted by applicable law, we shall provide you with e-mail notice, and opportunity to challenge the subpoena, prior to disclosure of any personal information pursuant to a subpoena; (iv) if we are sold, merge with a third party, are acquired or are the subject of bankruptcy proceedings; provided, however, that if we are involved in a bankruptcy proceeding, merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via e-mail and/or a prominent notice on the Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices that you may have regarding your personal information; and/or (v) when we deem it necessary or appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, and Federal Trade Commission implementing regulations. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, we reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute any and all personal information with/to any third party for any and all uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information Collection and Use
----------------------------------------------------------

Please see our [Privacy Provisions for California Residents](https://rounduprisk.com/ccpa/) below for more details regarding the categories and types of non-personal information collected.

Demographic Information and Aggregate Data
------------------------------------------

Aggregate and demographic data is data that describes the demographics, usage or characteristics of our Users as a group, without disclosing personally identifiable information. We use demographic information to tailor the Site Offerings to the interests of our Users. Demographic information is shared with third party advertisers so that they can tailor their advertisements to the appropriate audience. Demographic information may also be shared with other third parties.

We reserve the right to provide aggregate data about our Users for lawful purposes. By agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any aggregate data, record or communication to any third party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate.

Your IP Address
---------------

Each time that you visit the Site, our web server automatically recognizes your IP address and the web page from which you came. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you. We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer the Site and to better serve you in using the products, services and other features contained within the Site.

Cookies and Action Tags
-----------------------

Cookies
-------

The first time that a User provides an e-mail address in connection with her/his activities at the Site, we assign an identification number to that e-mail address and deploy a cookie to the applicable User’s PC. Whenever that User comes back to the Site using the same PC, the cookie allows the Site to identify the User and to recall the User’s e-mail address.

If, at any time, a User provides other information in connection with her/his activities on the Site (such as name, address, birth date, gender, etc.), we may store that information, along with the User’s e-mail address, in our User database. We may use the information stored in our database: (a) to effectuate the purpose or transaction for which the information was originally provided by a User; (b) to pre-populate information fields in the event that User wishes to purchase products and/or services or sign up for and/or subscribe to services, promotions or other offers in the future; (c) to ensure that a User will not be repeatedly exposed to the same advertisements, offers and/or promotions while visiting the Site; and/or (d) to, in connection with regular communication with a User, include offers, promotions or advertisements that were historically, or are likely to be, of interest to that User.

To find out more about cookies, please visit [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). To disable and reject cookies, adjust the settings via the toolbar options menu of your Internet browser. Cookies placed by members of the Digital Advertising Alliance may be opted out of by visiting [optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/). We reserve the right to retain this cookie data indefinitely, and to share information generated by these cookies with our advertisers, affiliates and service providers.

Action Tags, Web Beacons and other Data Collection Methods

An action tag or a web-beacon (also known as a clear gif or a pixel tag) is a method used to track responses or actions by visitors who view certain advertisements and/or other information on the Site. Action tags are 1×1 pixel images embedded in a website page that are used to transparently collect information. We may use action tags to count the number of times that visitors click on a particular banner ad or visit the pages of the Site and to provide information about what products/services are viewed or purchased. We reserve the right to retain this action tag data indefinitely, and to share information generated by these action tags with our advertisers, affiliates and service providers.

Behavioral Tracking
-------------------

Company uses cookies and other tracking technology on the Site for purposes of tracking Users’ activities after they leave the Site. Company uses this tracking technology to target applicable Users with advertisements regarding the Site Offerings and other products and/or services that Company thinks may be of interest to applicable Users. In addition, third parties, such as Google®, may engage in a similar form of behavioral tracking of Users that visit the Site.

If you wish to opt-out of having this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by emailing [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com). Users may also be able to disable some, but not all, of this tracking activity by utilizing the “Do Not Track” setting or similar options within most major Internet browsers. Further, Users may be able to opt-out of this form of tracking utilizing the options made available by the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) or [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Please note that opting out of this tracking activity does not opt you out of being served advertising. Even where you opt out of this tracking activity, you will continue to receive generic ads.

To the greatest extent permissible under applicable law, we are not responsible for the tracking practices of third parties in connection with the Site.

Other Websites
--------------

The Site Offerings may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites including, but not limited to, Social Media Websites and the websites of our Third-Party Legal Professionals. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be able to make a purchase through one of their third-party websites. In these instances, you may be required to provide certain information, such as a credit card number, to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and Company has no responsibility or liability relating to them.

Third-Party Offers
------------------

Company provides Users with the opportunity to receive special offers, products and/or services from third parties including, but not limited to, the Third-Party Legal Professionals. Where you indicate the desire to receive certain offers, products or services from a third party during the applicable information collection process, your personally identifiable information that was provided during that Company information collection process will be shared with the applicable third party so that such third party may provide its product or service to you and so that you do not have to complete another information collection form (or re-supply the same information) to purchase or receive that product or service.

Security of Your Personal Information
-------------------------------------

The privacy of your personal information is very important to us. As such, we endeavor to safeguard and protect our Users’ personal information. When Users make personal information available to us, their personal information is protected both online and offline (to the extent that we maintain any personal information offline). Where our registration/application process prompts Users to enter sensitive information (such as medical information, driver’s license/ID card number, health insurance information, data collected from an automated license plate recognition system, Social Security Number and credit card information), and when we store and transmit such sensitive information, that information is encrypted with advanced TLS (Transport Layer Security).

Access to your personal information is strictly limited, and we take reasonable measures to ensure that your personal information is not accessible to the public. The servers that we store personal information on are kept in a secure physical environment. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no storage facility, technology, software, security protocols or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

Computer hackers that circumvent our security measures may gain access to certain portions of your personal information, and technological bugs, errors and glitches may cause inadvertent disclosures of your personal information; provided, however, that any attempt to breach the security of the network, our servers, databases or other hardware or software constitutes a crime punishable by law. For the reasons mentioned above, we cannot warrant that your personal information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data by or through the Site Offerings is at your own risk.

All of our Users’ personal information is restricted in our offices. Only employees or third party agents who need personal information to perform a specific job function are granted access to personal information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all User personal information. Employees not adhering to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

Children’s Privacy
------------------

Please see our [Privacy Provisions for California Residents](https://rounduprisk.com/ccpa/) below for more details regarding the personal information of minors.

No information should be submitted to, or posted at, the Site by visitors under eighteen (18) years of age (or the applicable age of majority, if greater than eighteen (18) years of age in their respective jurisdictions). Persons eighteen (18) years of age (or the applicable age of majority, if greater than eighteen (18) years of age in their respective jurisdictions) are not permitted to access the Site Offerings and we do not knowingly collect personal information from such individuals. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

Removal, Amending and/or Updating Your Information
--------------------------------------------------

Please see our [Privacy Provisions for California Residents](https://rounduprisk.com/ccpa/) below for instructions on how California Residents can access and/or delete personal information that we have collected.

At your request, we will: (a) inform you of what personal information we have on file for you; (b) amend the personal information that we have on file for you; and/or (c) remove personal information that you have provided to us, or that we have collected. You may do so by contacting us via e-mail at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com); provided, however, that we ask individuals to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, amended or removed before processing such requests, and, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).

Please be further advised that, after you delete your personal information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.

Opt-Out; Unsubscribe
--------------------

Please see our [Privacy Provisions for California Residents](https://rounduprisk.com/ccpa/) below for instructions on how California Residents can opt-out of the sale of their personal information to third parties.

We provide Users with the ability to opt-out from receiving information sent via electronic mailings on or own behalf and that of our third party advertisers. Users may unsubscribe from receiving e-mail at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every e-mailing. Unsubscribe requests can only be processed by us if you have registered with us in the first instance. If you have not registered with us and wish to opt out of receiving e-mail from a particular sender, please consult that sender’s opt out policies or contact that sender.

To opt-out from email marketing, please email us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com)

Information sent on behalf of third party advertisers is prepared several days in advance, so Users may continue to receive e-mail from us for up to ten (10) days following our receipt of unsubscribe requests. If, after that point, a User is still receiving e-mail from us, the User should contact us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com)

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for purposes of communicating information relating to your request for Site Offerings, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you. To opt-out of receiving Site Offerings-related and/or inquiry response-related messages from us, you must cease requesting Site Offerings and cease submitting inquiries to us, as applicable.

Transfer of Personal Information Internationally
------------------------------------------------

If you are visiting the Site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with us may result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting the Site and/or otherwise communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers. Even if your jurisdiction does not have the same privacy laws as the jurisdiction where our servers are located, we will treat your information as subject to the protections described in this Privacy Policy.

Changes to this Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. If the manner in which we use personally identifiable information changes, we will notify Users by: (a) sending the modified policy to our Users via e-mail; and/or (b) by any other reasonable means acceptable under applicable state and federal law. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner, and we will only use your information in this different manner where you opt-in to such use.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of Company or your dealings with Company, please e-mail us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com); call us at: (833) 757-0886; or send us U.S. Mail to: 300 Carlsbad Village Dr. 108A-516, Carlsbad, CA 92008.

Filing a Complaint with the Federal Trade Commission

To file a complaint regarding our privacy practices, please [Click Here](https://reportfraud.ftc.gov/).

Privacy Provisions for California Residents
-------------------------------------------

These Privacy Provisions for California Residents (“Privacy Provisions”) supplement, and do not limit in any way, the Privacy Policy set forth above. These Privacy Provisions apply solely to residents of the State of California (“CA Users”). We adopt these Privacy Provisions in compliance with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”). Any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in these Privacy Provisions. Users with disabilities who wish to access these Privacy Provisions in an alternative format can contact us by emailing us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com); by calling us at: (833) 757-0886; or sending us U.S. Mail to: 300 Carlsbad Village Dr. 108A-516, Carlsbad, CA 92008.

Categories of Information We Collect
------------------------------------

We collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular CA User or device (“personal information”). In particular, we have collected the following categories of personal information from CA Users within the last twelve (12) months:

| Category | Examples | Collected |
| --- | --- | --- |
| A. Identifiers. | A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, telephone number, or other similar identifiers. | YES |
| B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)). | A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, postal address, telephone number, passport number, driver's license or State identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories. | YES |
| C. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law. | Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information). | YES |
| D. Commercial information. | Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. | NO  |
| E. Biometric information. | Genetic, physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics, or activity patterns used to extract a template or other identifier or identifying information, such as, fingerprints, faceprints, and voiceprints, iris or retina scans, keystroke, gait, or other physical patterns, and sleep, health, or exercise data. | NO  |
| F. Internet or other similar network activity. | Browsing history, search history, information on a CA User's interaction with a website, application or advertisement. | YES |

Personal information does not include:

* Publicly available information from government records.
    
* De-identified or aggregated CA User information.
    
* Information excluded from the CCPA's scope, such as:
    
    * oohealth or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data; and
        
    * oopersonal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA), and the Driver's Privacy Protection Act of 1994.

We obtain the categories of personal information listed above from the following categories of sources (with the specific categories of personal information indicated in parenthesis):

* Directly from our CA Users. For example, from online registration forms that our CA Users submit to us in connection with the products and/or services that we offer by and through the Site. (Categories A, B and C)
    
* Indirectly from our CA Users. For example, through information we collect from our CA Users in the course of providing our products and/or services to them. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* Directly and indirectly from activity on the Site. This includes the type of browser that the CA User uses (e.g., Safari, Chrome, Internet Explorer), CA User IP address, the type of operating system used by the CA User (e.g., Windows or iOS) and the domain name of the CA User’s Internet Service Provider. In addition, we obtain certain Site usage details and analytics as same are collected automatically by us and our third party partners. (Category F)
    
* When our CA Users interact with us on our social media accounts, including commenting on and/or liking our posts. (Category F)
    
* From third-parties that interact with us in connection with the products and/or services that we offer to our CA Users. For example, third party entities that assist us in sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from CA User lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. (Categories A, B, C and F)

Use of Personal Information
---------------------------

We may use or disclose the personal information that we collect (including: (a) name; (b) e-mail address; (c) telephone number; (d) zip code; (e) date of birth; (f) whether the User has already obtained legal representation; and/or (g) questions pertaining to the type of Legal Matter that the User is inquiring about) for one or more of the following business purposes (with the specific categories of personal information indicated in parenthesis):

* To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided. For example, if you provide us with personal information in connection with your purchase of products and/or services, we will use that information to process your order. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* To create, maintain, customize and secure your account with us. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* To provide you with e-mail, direct mail and telemarketing messages concerning certain Company products and/or services, as well as third-party products and/or services, that we believe may be of interest to you. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* To deliver relevant Site content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including the Site’s Terms and Conditions. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* To improve the Site and better present its contents to you. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* For customer service purposes and to respond to inquiries from you. (Categories A, B and C)
    
* For testing, research, analysis and product development. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* As necessary or appropriate to protect our rights, property or safety, and that of our clients and/or others. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the CCPA. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us is among the assets transferred. (Categories A, B, C and F)

We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information we collected for materially different, unrelated or incompatible purposes without providing you with notice.

Sharing Personal Information
----------------------------

Subject to your right to opt-out of such sharing/sale, we may share, rent and/or sell your personal information from Categories A, B, C and F (including: (a) name; (b) e-mail address; (c) telephone number; (d) zip code; (e) date of birth; (f) whether the User has already obtained legal representation; and/or (g) questions pertaining to the type of Legal Matter that the User is inquiring about): (i) with/to third parties for marketing purposes; and (ii) for the other business purposes set forth above.

When we disclose personal information to a third party service provider or other entity, we enter into a contractual relationship that describes the purpose for which such third party may use the personal information and requires that third party to both keep the personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose other than the performance of its services under the applicable contract. Please note, we do not collect information from CA Users that we actually know are less than eighteen (18) years of age and we do not share or sell the personal information of CA Users that we actually know are less than eighteen (18) years of age. Without limiting the foregoing, we have not shared or sold the personal information of CA Users that we actually know are less than sixteen (16) years of age in the preceding twelve (12) months.

In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have disclosed the following categories of personal information (including: (a) name; (b) e-mail address; (c) telephone number; (d) zip code; (e) date of birth; (f) whether the User has already obtained legal representation; and/or (g) questions pertaining to the type of Legal Matter that the User is inquiring about) for a business purpose:

Category A Identifiers.  
Category B California Customer Records personal information categories.  
Category C Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law.  
Category F Internet or other similar network activity.

We disclose your personal information for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties (with the specific categories of personal information indicated in parenthesis):

* Our affiliates. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* Service providers. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* Third parties who provide the products and/or services featured on the Site. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* Third parties who purchase and/or license your personal information for marketing purposes, including: (a) providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation; (b) e-mail marketers; (c) telemarketers (where permitted by applicable law); and (d) direct marketers. If a third party purchaser of your personal information wants to resell it, that purchaser is required by law to provide you with explicit notice and an opportunity to opt-out of further sales, unless the right to resell it was secured by us at the point of collection. (Categories A, B, C and F)
    
* Third parties to whom you authorize us to disclose your personal information in connection with the products and/or services that we provide to you. (Categories A, B, C and F)

In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have sold the following categories of personal information (including: (a) name; (b) e-mail address; (c) telephone number; (d) zip code; (e) date of birth; (f) whether the User has already obtained legal representation; and/or (g) questions pertaining to the type of Legal Matter that the User is inquiring about) to third parties:

Category A Identifiers.  
Category B California Customer Records personal information categories.  
Category C Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law.  
Category F Internet or other similar network activity.

In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have sold the above referenced categories of personal information to the third parties who purchase and/or license your personal information for marketing purposes, as well as the third parties who provide the products and/or services featured on the Site.

Your Rights and Choices
-----------------------

The CCPA provides CA Users (California residents) with specific rights regarding their personal information. This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights.

Opt-Out from the Sale of Your Personal Information

You have the right to opt-out of our sale of your personal information to third parties. To exercise your right to opt-out of our sale of your personal information to third parties, please submit a verifiable CA User request to us by either:

* [Clicking here](https://rounduprisk.com/ccpa/optout/);
    
* Emailing us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com); or
    
* Sending us U.S. Mail to: 300 Carlsbad Village Dr. 108A-516, Carlsbad, CA 92008.

We endeavor to act on all opt-out requests as soon as practicable, but in all cases within fifteen (15) business days of the receipt of your request.

Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights
----------------------------------------------------------

You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past twelve (12) months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable CA User request, we will disclose to you:

* The categories of personal information we collected about you.
    
* The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
    
* Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.
    
* The categories of third parties with whom we have shared that personal information.
    
* The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request).
    
* If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing:
    
    * sales, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased; and
        
    * disclosures for a business purpose, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained.

Deletion Request Rights
-----------------------

You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable CA User request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our (their) records, unless an exception applies; provided, however, that in some cases, strictly for regulatory compliance purposes and to better evidence/honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests (and for no other purposes), we may retain certain items of your personal information on a de-identified and aggregated basis in such a manner that the data no longer identifies you.

We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service providers to:

1. 1.Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our obligations in connection with our contract with you.
    
2. 2.Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
    
3. 3.Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
    
4. 4.Exercise free speech rights, ensure the right of another CA User to exercise her/his free speech rights or exercise another right provided for by law.
    
5. 5.Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 seq.).
    
6. 6.Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, but only if you previously provided informed consent.
    
7. 7.Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with CA User expectations based on your relationship with us.
    
8. 8.Comply with a legal obligation.
    
9. 9.Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.

Exercising Access, Data Portability and Deletion Rights
-------------------------------------------------------

To exercise your access, data portability and/or deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable CA User request to us by either:

* Emailing us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com); or
    
* Sending us U.S. Mail to: 300 Carlsbad Village Dr. 108A-516, Carlsbad, CA 92008.

Only you or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable CA User request related to your personal information.

You may only make a verifiable CA User request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable CA User request must:

* Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify that you are: (1) the person about whom we collected personal information; or (2) an authorized representative.
    
* Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm that the personal information relates to you. Making a verifiable CA User request does not require that you create an account with us. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable CA User request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.

Response Timing and Format
--------------------------

We endeavor to respond to all verifiable CA User requests within forty-five (45) days of the receipt thereof. If we require more time (up to ninety (90) days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing. We will deliver our written response by mail or electronically, at your option. Any disclosures that we provide will only cover the twelve (12) month period preceding the receipt of your verifiable request. The response that we provide will also explain the reasons that we cannot comply with a request, if applicable. For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information that is readily useable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.

We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable CA User request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.

Non-Discrimination
------------------

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:

* Deny you goods or services;
    
* Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties;
    
* Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services; and/or
    
* Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

Changes to these Privacy Provisions
-----------------------------------

We reserve the right to amend these Privacy Provisions in our discretion and at any time. When we make changes to these Privacy Provisions, we will notify you by email or through a notice on the Site’s homepage.

Contact Information
-------------------

If you have any questions or comments about these Privacy Provisions, our Privacy Policy, the ways in which we collect and use your personal information, your choices and rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your rights under California law, please do not hesitate to contact us by either:

* Emailing us at: [care@nationalinjurybureau.com](mailto:care@nationalinjurybureau.com); or
    
* Sending us U.S. Mail to: 300 Carlsbad Village Dr. 108A-516, Carlsbad, CA 92008.

Copyright © 2024 rounduprisk.com- All Rights Reserved.

PAID ATTORNEY ADVERTISEMENT: This Website is a group advertisement. It is not a lawyer referral service. rounduprisk.com is owned and operated by National Injury Bureau and is not a law firm. We connect people to legal service providers and there is no charge to be connected with an attorney. You are under no obligation to retain any services of those connected through our website. We try our best to keep things fair and balanced to help you make the best choice for you. This information does not constitute legal or medical advice and it should not be relied upon as such. Results are not guaranteed and past performance is not an indication of future success. Always consult with your doctor before modifying your medication or regular medical regimen.
